OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs UP249
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs
2007 -- 2011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Educational Affairs
UP249
0.5 Linear Feet
21 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs. The first OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Education Affairs was published in August, 2007. It is published six times a year. This collection consists of paper and electronic copies of the newsletter starting in 2007.
- OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2007 -- 2011; UP249.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 21 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs. The first OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Education Affairs was published in August, 2007. It is published six times a year.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2007; UP249.001.001.00001; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2007; UP249.001.001.00002; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    1, 2
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2007; UP249.001.001.00003; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    1, 3
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2008; UP249.001.001.00004; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    1, 4
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2008; UP249.001.001.00005; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    1, 5
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2008; UP249.001.001.00006; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    1, 6
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2008; UP249.001.001.00007; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    2, 1
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2008; UP249.001.001.00008; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    2, 2
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2009; UP249.001.001.00009; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    2, 3
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2009; UP249.001.001.00010; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    2, 4
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2009; UP249.001.001.00011; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    2, 5
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2009; UP249.001.001.00012; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    3, 1
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2009; UP249.001.001.00013; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    3, 2
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2010; UP249.001.001.00014; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    3, 3
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2010-04; UP249.001.001.00015; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    3, 4
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2010-06; UP249.001.001.00016; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    3, 5
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2010-09; UP249.001.001.00017; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    4, 1
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2010-11; UP249.001.001.00018; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    4, 2
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2011-01; UP249.001.001.00019; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    4, 3
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2011-04; UP249.001.001.00020; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    4, 4
  - OEA: Newsletter of the Office of Educational Affairs, 2011-06; UP249.001.001.00021; Office of Educational Affairs (Box 1)
    4, 5